<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HeisenBears</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open" translatable="false">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close" translatable="false">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id" translatable="false">1783378521921664</string>
    <string name="action_settings" translatable="false">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_acceuil">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_actu">News</string>
    <string name="menu_jeu">Game</string>
    <string name="menu_team">The team</string>
    <string name="menu_rescal">Results and Schedule</string>
    <string name="menu_profil">Profil</string>
    <string name="menu_propos">About</string>
    <string name="menu_deco">Log out</string>
    <string name="connexion">Log in with Facebook</string>
    <string name="Skip">Skip this</string>
    <string name="Connection">Connexion</string>
    <string name="visibility">Change visibility (visible)</string>
    <string name="invisibility">Change visibility (invisible)</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="profil">See and manage profil</string>
    <string name="information">Modify/add information</string>
    <string name="playbook">Playbook</string>
    <string name="notification">Send notification</string>
    <string name="group">Facebook group</string>
    <string name="page">Facebook page</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="salutation">Hey</string>
    <string name="signalement1">If you are a player, </string>
    <string name="signalement2">Clic here !</string>
    <string name="signalement3">You are \"signler\", wait ...</string>
    <string name="CoFacebook">You need to be connect with Facebook to do it !</string>
    <string name="signalementMessage">Done !</string>
    <string name="Text">Text</string>
    <string name="picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="video">Video</string>
    <string name="Select">Select</string>
    <string name="titre">Title</string>
    <string name="épingler">Pin</string>
    <string name="priver">Private</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling" translatable="false">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="send">send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_score" translatable="false">Score</string>
    <string name="Base">The basics of the game :   Football plays with 11 players in each teams with unlimited replacements. Each team owns an offensive and a defensive squad composed with 11 players each having his use in the game. The goal when you possess the ball is to make it go further towards the oponents’ end-zone. The team that does not own the football must then keep them from achieving their objective and score points. A game is set in four 20 minutes quarter-times with a 15 minutes pause in between the second and third quarter-times.</string>
    <string name="Deroulement">Conduct of a game :   A kick-off is made by one of the teams at the beginning of both half-times. The other team catches the football and tries to get it as far as possible from their end-zone until they get tackled or they score. This part is called kickoff return. The tackling spot marks the departure place for the offensive team. Then they have 4 attempts (downs) in order to get the football 10 yards (9.10m) further,  either with passes or running on the ground. If they manage to make it, they earn the first down and 4 attemps again. And so on. If they can’t do it, then the possesion switches and the team must defend.  In the case where there is still a lot of field to cover for an offense that is on 4th down,  the offense can decide to give-up the possession and punt the football far away, it is the same objective than the kick-off.</string>
    <string name="LeScore">Scoring :  There are three ways to score in football :  -Touchdown (TD) : It is worth 6 points and can be scored by reaching the oponents’ end-zone with the football under control. A special play is set-up right after that, allowing the offense team to score either one more point by kicking the ball between the poles or two points if they mnage to score a TD on this play. -Field-Goal : A kick between the poles that gives 3 points. -Safety : Rather rare action, it is worth 2 points if the football owner gets tackled in his own end-zone.</string>
    <string name="PostesAtt">1)\tOffensive squad : Quarterback (QB) : He is the star player of the team, he calls the games for his team and leads the offensive squad on the field. He decides if the team must run on the ground or pass on the air. When he doesn’t play, he is still useful since he helps the coaches  and analyzes the opponent’s games.  Offnesive linemen (OL) : Spotted just ahead of the QB on the beginning of the game, they are his bodyguards. The curtain of 5 heavy players buying some time for their teammate allowing him to transmit the ball without pressure.  Tight-end (TE) : He is spotted right besides the OL. He is a very complete player, he must be able to run, receive a pass and make blocks on other players.  Running back (RB) : Often spotted on a side of the QB, these players have the duty to take the ball right after the snap and to push it as far as possible while running. They can also be a deceive or block an oponent.  Wide receiver (WR) : Specialists of pass reception at different distances, they are usually placed on the wings of the field in order to give them some space to work with. They often take the most field distance for their teams.</string>
    <string name="PostesDef">2)\tDefensive squad Defensive Linemen (DL) : Directly opposed to the OL, they must disrupt the oposing offense by blocking the transmission or of the ball owner. Their second role is to communicate to ther team what happens in front of them. Indeed, they are the first to see if the oponents want to run or pass.  Linebackers (LB) : The second defensive curtain. These players must cover the DL’s back, if something passes in their zone, they must stop it.  Cornerbacks (CB/DB) : The CB’s are quick players, their goal is to keep the pass games with the WR. They are often responsible for interceptions.  Safety (S) :  Lhe S are the last fortifications of a defensive formation. Once passed, there is nothing left to stop the ball owner. Their role is therefore to intercept the long passes and to come backup LBs if the ball owner goes through.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_apropos">About</string>
    <string name="aPropos">This application was developped by Fontaine Thomas and Tatou Noufele for their school project.</string>
    <string name="poid">Weight :</string>
    <string name="taille">Height :</string>
</resources>
